You have 3 seconds to guess where
we are 3 2 1
We are at the beach, look, here it is.
the beach
[Music]
We came to have a relaxing day of
beach the first thing I do when I come to
the beach is to lay the towel on the ground
Normally the beach is sandy.
beach as you can see is made of stones
They can be very good for playing and for
make mountains out of stone cities
he also to play but to be
comfortably lying on the beach is not
so well with which -as I understand the
towel over the stones I make sure
that there is no stone too large
big
we just want little stones
because if there are big stones, they will go away.
to nail in the back and we are not going to
relax we are going to be very uncomfortable
It's worth trying to guess what song it is.
this
Leave me a comment which song you think
I love to sing Christmas carols in the middle of
summer
I went to see a donkey ring ring I
I was mending myself, I was mending myself, that a
I already took off the patch, I appreciate it.
sound of ocean waves
I sunbathe
The only thing I don't like about wearing
cream is that it is very sticky
I usually put on sunscreen
at home and so when I come to the beach
I have it on but I didn't wear it today
position because I was going to come and see the
dawn but I fell asleep and the
the sun is already up there
one
When I'm very hot it's right in
this moment that
I'm running
into the water and take a bath in the hammer
[Applause]
It depends on how cold the water is
It takes me more or less time to go in to bathe if
It's very cold, it took a long time or it didn't take long at all.
nothing and water and the duration of my bath and
The water is from the Atlantic Ocean
north then my bath lasts about 15
seconds if the water is from the Mediterranean
so my bath can last up to a
hour of the hours
[Music]
[Applause]
Once I get out of the water on this beach,
One of the things I do is to plunder myself.
heels I use the stones from this
beaches that have holes have holes
They use the stones of this beach to
rub my heel and exfoliate it
It's a very good practice I'm going to do
a demonstration but with your hands
first plundered the foot against the
arena
We rub the egg against the rock
our choice
Other things I do at the beach are
play with the sand
[Music]
[Applause]
ok what do you think that done
[Music]
At first it was going to be a donut but
then I realized that also
can be a lifesaver
but I prefer a pain
and most importantly and rewardingly, eat
Peeling requires an art that I don't
I have
it just is
It's not being treated as I thought
I'm going to clean the knife to
wash my hands
[Music]
You can also read a book in my
In case I'm traveling I don't have any books.
physicists with which I read on the mobile that
By the way, last week we did the
first meeting of our club
reading you are more than welcome to come
I can't see anything but I'm reading
and
[Music]